Mr. Emmanuel Wabbi's church mark in the middle of time, Mark Ariyne I saw Miami police and that idea is not going to take
on a five as consent agenda staff is recommending the six and seven which are claims in minutes.
There were no questions all needed those items that they're taking to motion two approve, motion approved
second? Second for roll call please
I don't need any business or business it's a reason
I don't know if there's a reason for the posting.
Item nine is staff reports, they're in your packet item ten and trustee community announcements
Any questions anyone?
Adam 11 as adjournment we have motion two adjourned
Second
Mark it
All right